<NEWS>
<!--Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or morecontributor license agreements. See the NOTICE file distributed withthis work for additional information regarding copyright ownership.The ASF licenses this file to You under the Apache License, Version 2.0(the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance withthe License. You may obtain a copy of the License athttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, softwaredistributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.See the License for the specific language governing permissions andlimitations under the License. -->
<DOCS>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>126</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>B12
</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Special Liver-Stomach Concentrate (containing Intrinsic Factor)  240mg, Vitamin B 12 (activity equivalent)  15mcg, 
Iron and Elemental (as Ferrous Fumarate)  110mg, Ascorbic Acid (Vitamin C)  75 mg, Folic Acid  0.5 mg, D&C Red #28, 
FD&C Blue #1, FD&C Red #40, gelatin, magnesium stearate, povidone, silicon dioxide, sodium lauryl sulfate, starch and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
A Highly Potent Oral Antianemia Preparation
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>127</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BabyBIG</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
FSolvent-detergent-treated, sterile, lyophilized powder of immunoglobulin G (IgG), 
stabilized with 5% sucrose and 1% albumin (human), no preservative.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BabyBIG , Botulism Immune Globulin Intravenous (Human), is indicated for the treatment 
of infant botulism caused by toxin type A or B in patients below one year of age.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>128</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BACiiM</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
 injection, powder, lyophilized
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bacitracin for Injection, USP is a sterile antibiotic for intramuscular administration. 
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>129</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bacillus</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
glycerin, asparagine, citric acid, potassium phosphate, magnesium sulfate, and iron ammonium citrate, lactose.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BCG (Bacillus Calmette and Guérin) is a freeze-dried product made from bacteria. 
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>130</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Baclofen</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
aspartame, colloidal silicon dioxide, crospovidone, magnesium stearate, mannitol, 
microcrystalline cellulose, natural and artificial orange flavor and povidone.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Baclofen is useful for the alleviation of signs and symptoms of spasticity resulting from multiple sclerosis, 
particularly for the relief of flexor spasms and concomitant pain, clonus, and muscular rigidity
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>131</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BalancedSalt </PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
hypromellose, sodium chloride, potassium chloride, dibasic sodium phosphate, sodium bicarbonate, 
hydrochloric acid and/or sodium hydroxide, calcium chloride, magnesium chloride, dextrose, gluthathione disulfide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Balanced salt is indicated for use as an intraocular irrigating solution during surgical procedures 
involving perfusion of the eye
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>132</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BaloxavirMarboxil</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
croscarmellose sodium, hypromellose, lactose monohydrate, microcrystalline cellulose, 
povidone, sodium stearyl fumarate, talc, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Baloxavir marboxil is indicated for the treatment of acute uncomplicated influenza in patients 
12 years of age and older who have been symptomatic for no more than 48 hours.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>133</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BalsalazideDisodium</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
colloidal silicon dioxide, magnesium stearate, 750 mg of balsalazide disodium, 
mesalamine (5-aminosalicylic acid or 5-ASA), and an anti-inflammatory drug
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Balsalazide disodium is indicated for the treatment of mildly to moderately 
active ulcerative colitis in patients 5 years of age and older. 
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>134</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BALVERSA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Glycerol monocaprylocaprate Type I, Polyvinyl alcohol-partially hydrolyzed, Sodium lauryl sulfate, Talc, Titanium dioxide, Iron oxide yellow, 
Iron oxide red (for the orange and brown tablets only), Ferrosoferric oxide/iron oxide black (for the brown tablets only).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BALVERSA is indicated for the treatment of adult patients with locally advanced or metastatic urothelial carcinoma (mUC)
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>135</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Balziva</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
norethindrone, ethinyl estradiol, 0.4 mg norethindrone, USP and 0.035 mg ethinyl estradiol, USP, and contain the following 
inactive ingredients: anhydrous lactose, dibasic calcium phosphate, FD&C yellow no. 6 aluminum lake, lactose monohydrate, 
magnesium stearate, povidone and sodium starch glycolate, lactose monohydrate, magnesium stearate, and pregelatinized corn starch.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Balziva are indicated for the prevention of pregnancy in women who elect to use this product as a method of contraception.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>136</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BANZEL</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
colloidal silicon dioxide, corn starch crosscarmellose sodium, hypromellose, 
lactose monohydrate, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose, and sodium lauryl sulphate, 
hypromellose, iron oxide red, polyethylene glycol, talc, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BANZEL is indicated for adjunctive treatment of seizures associated with 
Lennox-Gastaut Syndrome in pediatric patients 1 year of age and older and in adults.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>137</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BARACLUDE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
lactose monohydrate, microcrystalline cellulose, crospovidone, povidone, magnesium stearate, 
titanium dioxide, hypromellose, polyethylene glycol 400, polysorbate 80, and iron oxide red.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BARACLUDE (entecavir) is indicated for the treatment of chronic hepatitis B virus infection in adults and pediatric patients 2 years of age
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>138</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Baricitinib</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
croscarmellose sodium, magnesium stearate, mannitol, microcrystalline cellulose, 
ferric oxide, lecithin (soya), polyethylene glycol, polyvinyl alcohol, talc and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bericitinib is indicated for the treatment of adult patients with moderately to severely active 
rheumatiod arthritis who have had an inadequate response to one or more tumor necrosis factor (TNF) antagonist therapies.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>139</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BASAGLAR</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
30 mcg zinc, 2.7 mg metacresol, 17 mg glycerin, and water for injection.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BASAGLAR is indicated to improve glycemic control in adults and pediatric patients with 
type 1 diabetes mellitus and in adults with type 2 diabetes mellitus.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>140</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Basiliximab
</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
20 mg basiliximab, 7.21 mg monobasic potassium phosphate, 0.99 mg disodium hydrogen 
phosphate (anhydrous), 1.61 mg sodium chloride, 20 mg sucrose, 80 mg mannitol and 
40 mg glycine, to be reconstituted in 5 mL of Sterile Water for Injection, USP.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Basiliximab is indicated for the prophylaxis of acute organ rejection in patients 
receiving renal transplantation when used as part of an immunosuppressive regimen 
that includes cyclosporine, USP (MODIFIED) and corticosteroids.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>141</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BAVENCIO</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
20 mg avelumab, D-mannitol (51 mg), glacial acetic acid (0.6 mg), 
polysorbate 20 (0.5 mg), sodium hydroxide (0.3 mg), and Water for Injection.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BAVENCIO  is indicated for the treatment of adults and pediatric 
patients 12 years and older with metastatic Merkel cell carcinoma (MCC).
</TEXT>
</DOC>
<DOC>

<DOCNO>142</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BAXDELA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
450 mg delafloxacin (equivalent to 649 mg delafloxacin meglumine) and the following 
inactive ingredients: Citric acid anhydrous (5.5 mg); crospovidone (109 mg); magnesium 
stearate (10 mg); microcrystalline cellulose (417 mg); povidone (34 mg); 
sodium bicarbonate (140 mg); sodium phosphate monobasic monohydrate (5.5 mg).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BAXDELA is indicated in adults for the treatment of acute bacterial skin and skin 
structure infections (ABSSSI) caused by susceptible isolates.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>143</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_BAYCOL</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
cerivastatin sodium,  mannitol, magnesium stearate, sodium hydroxide, crospovidone, povidone, 
iron oxide yellow, methylhydroxypropylcellulose, polyethylene glycol, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BAYCOL is indicated as an adjunct to diet to reduce elevated Total-C, LDL-C, apo B, and TG and 
to increase HDL-C levels in patients with primary hypercholesterolemia and mixed dyslipidemia 
(Fredrickson Types IIa and IIb) when the response to dietary restriction of saturated fat and 
cholesterol and other non-pharmacological measures alone has been inadequate.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>144</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bayer</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
carnauba wax*, corn starch, hypromellose, powdered cellulose, triacetin
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Uses for headache, menstrual pain, minor pain of arthritis, muscle pain, 
pain and fever of colds, toothache
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>145</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BayGam™ Immune Globulin (Human)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
0.3% tri-n-butyl phosphate (TNBP) and 0.2% sodium cholate, formulated as a 
15–18% protein solution at a pH of 6.4–7.2 in 0.21–0.32 M glycine.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Immune Globulin (Human) — BayGam™ (immune globulin) treated with solvent/detergent is a 
sterile solution of immune globulin for intramuscular administration; it contains no preservative.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>146</DOCNO>
<HEADLINE>
of 0.3% tri-n-butyl phosphate (TNBP) and 0.2% sodium cholate, is formulated 
as a 15–18% protein solution at a pH of 6.4–7.2 in 0.21–0.32 M glycine.
<TEXT>
Recommendations on post-exposure prophylaxis are based on available efficacy data 
and on the likelihood of future HBV exposure for the person requiring treatment.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>147</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BayRab®(Rabies Immune Globulin (Human) Solvent/Detergent Treated)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
0.3% tri-n-butyl phosphate ( TNBP) and 0.2% sodium cholate, a 
15–18% protein solution at a pH of 6.4–7.2 in 0.21–0.32 M glycine.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Rabies vaccine and BayRab (rabies immune globulin (human) solvent/detergent treated) should be 
given to all persons suspected of exposure to rabies with one exception: persons who have been previously 
immunized with rabies vaccine and have a confirmed adequate rabies antibody titer should receive only vaccine
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>148</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BayTet®(Tetanus Immune Globulin (Human) Solvent/Detergent Treated 250 Units)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
0.3% tri-n-butyl phosphate (TNBP) and 0.2% sodium cholate, 15–18% protein solution at a pH of 6.4–7.2 in 0.21–0.32 M glycine
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BayTet (tetanus immune globulin (human) solvent/detergent treated 250 units) is indicated for prophylaxis against 
tetanus following injury in patients whose immunization is incomplete or uncertain (see below).
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>149</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>TheraCys®[BCG Live (Intravesical)]</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
potatoes, glycerine, asparagine, citric acid, potassium phosphate, magnesium sulfate, ferric 
ammonium citrate, calcium chloride, copper sulfate, and zinc sulfate, monosodium glutamate 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
TheraCys is indicated for intravesical use in the treatment and prophylaxis of carcinoma in situ 
(CIS) of the urinary bladder and for the prophylaxis of primary or recurrent stage Ta and/or T1 
papillary tumors following transurethral resection (TUR).
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>150</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>REGRANEX®(becaplermin) Gel</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
carboxymethylcellulose sodium, glacial acetic acid, l-lysine hydrochloride, m-cresol, methylparaben, 
propylparaben, sodium acetate trihydrate, sodium chloride, and water for injection, becaplermin.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
REGRANEX gel is indicated for the treatment of lower extremity diabetic neuropathic ulcers that extend into 
the subcutaneous tissue or beyond and have an adequate blood supply, when used as an adjunct to, and not a 
substitute for, good ulcer care practices including initial sharp debridement, pressure relief and infection control.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>150</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>QVAR®(beclomethasone dipropionate HFA) Metered Aerosol</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
QVAR 40 mcg Inhalation Aerosol and QVAR 80 mcg Inhalation Aerosol is beclomethasone dipropionate, USP, a corticosteroid 
having the chemical name 9-chloro-11ß,17,21- trihydroxy-16ß-methylpregna-1,4-diene-3,20-dione 17,21-dipropionate. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
QVAR is indicated in the maintenance treatment of asthma as prophylactic therapy in patients 5 years of age and older.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>151</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Baconase (Baclomethasone Nasal)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
9-chloro-11b,17,21-trihydroxy-16b-methylpregna-1,4-diene-3,20-doine17,21-dipropionate.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
bACONASE is indicated in the relief of the symptoms of seasonal or perennial allergic and nonallergic 
(vasomotor) rhinitis in those cases poorly responsive to conventional treatment.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>152</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bedaquiline Tablets</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
colloidal silicon dioxide, corn starch, croscarmellose sodium, hypromellose 2910 15 mPa.s, lactose monohydrate, 
magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose, polysorbate 20, purified water (removed during processing)
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bedaquiline Tablets is a diarylquinoline antimycobacterial drug indicated as part of combination therapy in 
the treatment of adults (18 years and older) with pulmonary multi-drug resistant tuberculosis (MDR-TB).
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>153</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bekyree (Desogestrel and Ethinyl Estradiol Tablets)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
0.15 mg desogestrel (13- ethyl-11-methylene-18,19-dinor-17 alpha-pregn-4-en- 20-yn-17-ol), 0.02 mg ethinyl estradiol 
(19-nor- 17 alpha-pregna-1,3,5 (10)-trien-20-yne-3,17-diol), and inactive ingredients which include colloidal silicon 
dioxide, corn starch, lactose monohydrate, magnesium stearate, povidone, stearic acid, talc, vitamin E and opadry white, 
a film coating made of hypromellose, polyethylene glycol, and titanium dioxide, followed by 2 inert green round biconvex 
tablets with the following inactive ingredients: corn starch, lactose monohydrate, magnesium stearate, and opadry green, 
a film coating made of D&C Yellow No. 10 Aluminum Lake, FD&C Blue No. 2 Aluminum Lake, FD&C Yellow No. 6 Aluminum Lake, 
hypromellose, polyethylene glycol, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bekyree (desogestrel and ethinyl estradiol tablets USP and ethinyl estradiol tablets USP) are indicated for the prevention 
of pregnancy in women who elect to use this product as a method of contraception.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>154</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>(belatacept) for Injection</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
intravenous administration, monobasic sodium phosphate (34.5 mg), sodium chloride (5.8 mg), and sucrose (500 mg).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
(belatacept) is indicated for prophylaxis of organ rejection in adult patients receiving a kidney transplant. 
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>155</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BELBUCA™(buprenorphine) Buccal Film</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
buprenorphine hydrochloride, a partial opioid agonist, consisting of a white to off-white backing layer with strength 
identifier printed in black ink and a light yellow to yellow active mucoadhesive layer containing buprenorphine hydrochloride.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BELBUCA is indicated for the management of pain severe enough to require daily, around-the-clock, long-term opioid treatment 
and for which alternative treatment options are inadequate.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>156</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BELEODAQ</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
500 mg belinostat as the active ingredient, 1000 mg L-Arginine, USP as an inactive ingredient, 250 mL of sterile 0.9% Sodium Chloride
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Beleodaq is indicated for the treatment of patients with relapsed or refractory peripheral T-cell lymphoma (PTCL).
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>157</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BENLYSTA(belimumab) for Injection</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
200 mg belimumab, L-arginine hydrochloride (5.3 mg), L-histidine (0.65 mg), L-histidine monohydrochloride (1.2 mg), 
polysorbate 80 (0.1 mg), and sodium chloride (6.7 mg).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BENLYSTA (belimumab) is indicated for the treatment of adult patients with active, autoantibody-positive, systemic 
lupus erythematosus (SLE) who are receiving standard therapy.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>158</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Benralizumab</PROFILE>


<HEADLINE>
30 mg benralizumab, L-histidine (1.4 mg); L-histidine hydrochloride monohydrate (2.3 mg); 
polysorbate 20 (0.06 mg); α,α-trehalose dihydrate (95 mg); and Water for Injection, USP. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Benralizumab is indicated for the add-on maintenance treatment of patients with severe asthma aged 12 years and older, and with an eosinophilic phenotype.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>158</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_BENTYL®(dicyclomine hydrochloride) Capsules</PROFILE>


<HEADLINE>
calcium sulfate, corn starch, FD&C Blue No. 1, FD&C Red No. 40, gelatin, lactose, magnesium stearate, pregelatinized corn starch, and 
titanium dioxide, acacia, dibasic calcium phosphate, corn starch, FD&C Blue No. 1, lactose, magnesium stearate, pregelatinized corn starch, and sucrose.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BENTYL® (dicyclomine hydrochloride) is indicated for the treatment of patients with functional bowel/irritable bowel syndrome.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>159</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BenzaClin® Topical Gel</PROFILE>


<HEADLINE>
clindamycin phosphate, (7(S)-chloro-7deoxylincomycin-2-phosphate), benzoyl peroxide, 10 mg (1%) clindamycin as phosphate and 
50 mg (5%) benzoyl peroxide in a base of carbomer, sodium hydroxide, dioctyl sodium sulfosuccinate, and purified water.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BenzaClin (clindamycin and benzoyl peroxide) Topical Gel is indicated for the topical treatment of acne vulgaris.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>160</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Benzagel (benzoyl peroxide gel)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
 50 mg and 100 mg respectively, of benzoyl peroxide in a gel vehicle of purified water, carbomer 940, 
 14% alcohol, sodium hydroxide, docusate sodium and fragrances.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Benzagel (benzoyl peroxide gel) may be used alone topically for mild to moderate acne and as an adjunct in acne treatment regimens 
which might include retinoic acid products, systemic antibiotics, and/or sulfur and salicylic acid containing preparations.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>161</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BenzamycinPak</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
erythromycin [(3R*, 4S*, 5S*, 6R*, 7R*, 9R*, 11R*, 12R*, 13S*, 14R*)-4-[(2,6- dideoxy-3-C-methyl-3-O-methyl-a- L-ribo-hexopyranosyl)-oxy]-
14- ethyl-7,12,13-trihydroxy- 3,5,7,9,11,13-hexa-methyl-6-[ [3,4,6-trideoxy-3-(dimethylamino)-b-D- xylo-hexopyranosyl] oxy]oxacyclotetradecane-2,10- dione
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BENZAMYCIN (erythromycin) Topical Gel is indicated for the topical treatment of acne vulgaris.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>162</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Benzhydrocodone and acetaminophen</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / UK consumer credit growth at six-year low
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
 6.12 mg of benzhydrocodone (equivalent to 6.67 mg benzhydrocodone hydrochloride) and 325 mg of acetaminophen, 
 crospovidone, microcrystalline cellulose, pregelatinized starch, Povidone K30, and stearic acid.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>163</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BENZNIDAZOLE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
12.5 mg or 100 mg of benznidazole, magnesium stearate, NF; microcrystalline cellulose, NF; monohydrate lactose, 
NF; pre-gelatinized corn starch, NF; and sodium croscarmellose, NF.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Benznidazole Tablets are indicated in pediatric patients 2 to 12 years of age for the treatment of 
Chagas disease (American trypanosomiasis) caused by Trypanosoma cruzi.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>164</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Benzocaine</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
benzocaine 20%, benzethonium chloride 0.1% , polyethylene glycol 300 and 3350.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Benzocaine is indicated for general use as a lubricant and topical anesthetic on intratracheal catheters 
and pharyngeal and nasal airways to obtund the pharyngeal and tracheal reflexes
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>165</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BENZONATATE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
100 mg or 200 mg of benzonatate, USP, D&C Yellow No. 10, gelatin, glycerin, methylparaben sodium and propylparaben sodium
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Benzonatate is indicated for the symptomatic relief of cough
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>166</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Benzagel (benzoyl peroxide gel)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
50 mg and 100 mg respectively, of benzoyl peroxide in a gel vehicle of purified water, 
carbomer 940, 14% alcohol, sodium hydroxide, docusate sodium and fragrances.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Benzagel (benzoyl peroxide gel) may be used alone topically for mild to moderate acne and as an adjunct in acne treatment regimens 
which might include retinoic acid products, systemic antibiotics, and/or sulfur and salicylic acid containing preparations.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>167</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Benzphetamine hydrochloride</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Calcium Stearate, Corn Starch, Erythrosine Sodium. FD & C Yellow No. 6, Lactose, Povidone, Sorbitol.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Benzphetamine hydrochloride are indicated in the management of exogenous obesity as a short term (a few weeks) 
adjunct in a regimen of weight reduction.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>168</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bepridil hydrochloride</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
hydroxypropyl methylcellulose, lactose, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose, polyethylene glycol, 
silicon dioxide, pregelatinized corn starch, corn starch, titanium dioxide, FD&C Blue #1. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bepridil hydrochloride is indicated for the treatment of chronic stable angina (classic effort-associated angina)
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>169</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Beractant</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
phospholipids, neutral lipids, fatty acids, and surfactant-associated proteins to which colfosceril palmitate(dipalmitoylphosphatidylcholine), 
palmitic acid, tripalmitin, 25 mg/mL phospholipids (including 11.0-15.5 mg/mL disaturated phosphatidylcholine), 0.5- 1.75 mg/mL triglycerides, 
1.4-3.5 mg/mL free fatty acids, and less than 1.0 mg/mL protein, 0.9% sodium chloride solution, 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Beractant is indicated for prevention and treatment (“rescue”) of Respiratory Distress Syndrome (RDS) (hyaline membrane disease) in premature 
infants. SURVANTA significantly reduces the incidence of RDS, mortality due to RDS and air leak complications.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>170</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_BETAGAN</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
levobunolol HCl 0.25% or 0.5%, benzalkonium chloride 0.004%, edetate disodium, polyvinyl alcohol 1.4%, potassium phosphate, monobasic, 
purified water, sodium chloride, sodium metabisulfite, sodium phosphate, dibasic, and hydrochloric acid or sodium hydroxide to adjust pH.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BETAGAN® ophthalmic solution has been shown to be effective in lowering intraocular pressure and may be used in patients with chronic 
open-angle glaucoma or ocular hypertension.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>171</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Betaine anhydrous</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
granular, hygroscopic powder, which is diluted in water and administered orally
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Betaine anhydrous is indicated for the treatment of homocystinuria to decrease elevated homocysteine blood concentrations 
in pediatric and adult patients
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>172</DOCNO>
<PROFILE> Betamethasone (DIPROLENE AF)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
0.643 mg betamethasone dipropionate USP (equivalent to 0.5 mg betamethasone) in a white 
cream base of carbomer 940; ceteareth-30; chlorocresol; cyclomethicone; glyceryl oleate/propylene glycol; 
propylene glycol; purified water; sodium hydroxide; sorbitol solution; white petrolatum; and white wax.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Betamethasone (DIPROLENE AF) is a corticosteroid indicated for the relief of the inflammatory and 
pruritic manifestations of corticosteroid-responsive dermatoses in patients 13 years of age or older.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>173</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BETAPACE(sotalol hydrochloride)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
microcrystalline cellulose, lactose, starch, stearic acid, magnesium stearate, colloidal silicon dioxide, 
and FD&C blue color #2 (aluminum lake, conc), microcrystalline cellulose, lactose, starch, 
stearic acid, magnesium stearate, and colloidal silicon dioxide. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Betapace/Betapace AF is indicated for the treatment of life-threatening, 
documented ventricular arrhythmias, such as sustained ventricular tachycardia (VT).
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>174</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BETHANECHOL CHLORIDE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
5 mg, 10 mg, 25 mg or 50 mg bethanechol chloride, colloidal silicon dioxide, lactose 
monohydrate, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose, sodium starch glycolate, (25 mg and 50 mg)
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bethanechol chloride is indicated for the treatment of acute postoperative and postpartum nonobstructive 
(functional) urinary retention and for neurogenic atony of the urinary bladder with retention.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>175</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BETHKIS</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
300 mg dose of tobramycin, sodium chloride and sulfuric acid.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BETHKIS is indicated for the management of cystic fibrosis patients with Pseudomonas aeruginosa.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>176</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Betimol</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
2.56 mg of timolol hemihydrate, monosodium, disodium phosphate dihydrate, benzalkonium chloride 0.01%
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Betimol is indicated in the treatment of elevated intraocular pressure in patients with ocular hypertension or open-angle glaucoma.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>177</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Betrixaban</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
dextrose monohydrate, croscarmellose sodium, magnesium stearate, and a hard gelatin capsule
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Betrixaban is indicated for the prophylaxis of venous thromboembolism (VTE) in adult 
patients hospitalized for an acute medical illness who are at risk for thromboembolic 
complications due to moderate or severe restricted mobility and other risk factors for VTE 
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>178</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bevacizumab</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
240 mg α,α-trehalose dihydrate, 23.2 mg sodium phosphate (monobasic, monohydrate), 
4.8 mg sodium phosphate (dibasic, anhydrous), 1.6 mg polysorbate 20, and Water
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bevacizumab is vascular endothelial growth factor directed antibody.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>179</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BEVYXXA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
dextrose monohydrate, croscarmellose sodium, magnesium stearate, and a hard gelatin capsule.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BEVYXXA is indicated for the prophylaxis of venous thromboembolism (VTE) in adult patients 
hospitalized for an acute medical illness who are at risk for thromboembolic complications 
due to moderate or severe restricted mobility and other risk factors for VTE
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>180</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bexarotene</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
polyethylene glycol 400, NF, polysorbate 20, NF, povidone, USP, and butylated hydroxyanisole, 
NF, gelatin, sorbitol special-glycerin blend, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bexarotene capsules are indicated for the treatment of cutaneous manifestations of cutaneous T-cell 
lymphoma in patients who are refractory to at least one prior systemic therapy.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>181</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BEXSERO</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
50 micrograms each of recombinant proteins Neisserial adhesin A (NadA), Neisserial Heparin Binding Antigen (NHBA), 
and factor H binding protein (fHbp), 25 micrograms of Outer Membrane Vesicles (OMV), 
1.5 mg aluminum hydroxide (0.519 mg of Al3+), 3.125 mg sodium chloride, 0.776 mg histidine, and 10 mg sucrose at pH 6.4 - 6.7.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BEXSERO is a vaccine indicated for active immunization to prevent invasive disease caused by Neisseria meningitidis serogroup B.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>182</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BEXTRA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
lactose monohydrate, microcrystalline cellulose, pregelatinized starch, croscarmellose sodium, magnesium stearate, 
hypromellose, polyethylene glycol, polysorbate 80, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
For relief of the signs and symptoms of osteoarthritis and adult rheumatoid arthritis, For the treatment of primary dysmenorrhea.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>183</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BEXXAR</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
 0.9 to 1.3 mg/mL ascorbic acid, 1 to 2 mg/mL maltose (dosimetric dose) or 9 to 15 mg/mL maltose (therapeutic dose), 
 4.4% to 6.6% (w/v) povidone, and 8.5 to 9.5 mg/mL sodium chloride. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
The BEXXAR therapeutic regimen (tositumomab and iodine I 131 tositumomab) is indicated for the treatment of patients 
with CD20-positive relapsed or refractory, low grade, follicular, or transformed non-Hodgkin's lymphoma who have 
progressed during or after rituximab therapy, including patients with rituximab-refractory non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>184</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bezlotoxumab</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
citric acid monohydrate (0.8 mg), diethylenetriaminepentaacetic acid (0.0078 mg), polysorbate 80 (0.25 mg), 
sodium chloride (8.77 mg), sodium citrate dihydrate (4.75 mg), and Water for Injection, USP. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bezlotoxumab is indicated to reduce recurrence of Clostridium difficile infection (CDI) in patients 18 years 
of age or older who are receiving antibacterial drug treatment of CDI and are at a high risk for CDI recurrence.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>185</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bicalutamide</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
 lactose, magnesium stearate, hypromellose, polyethylene glycol, polyvidone, sodium starch glycollate, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bicalutamide is indicated for use in combination therapy with a luteinizing hormone-releasing hormone (LHRH) analog for 
the treatment of Stage D2 metastatic carcinoma of the prostate.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>186</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BIDIL(isosorbide dinitrate and hydralazine hydrochloride) </PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
20 mg of isosorbide dinitrate and 37.5 mg of hydralazine hydrochloride, anhydrous lactose, 
microcrystalline cellulose, sodium starch glycolate, colloidal silicon dioxide, magnesium stearate, hypromellose, 
FD&C Yellow No. 6 aluminum lake, polyethylene glycol, titanium dioxide, polysorbate 80.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BiDil is indicated for the treatment of heart failure as an adjunct to standard therapy in self-identified black 
patients to improve survival, to prolong time to hospitalization for heart failure, and to improve patient-reported functional status.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>187</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BiferaRx</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Microcrystalline cellulose, croscarmellose sodium, crospovidone, magnesium stearate, silicon dioxide, coating (polyvinyl 
alcohol, polyethylene glycol, talc, FD&C red no. 40 aluminum lake, titanium dioxide, FD&C blue no. 2 aluminum lake).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BiferaRx is a prescription iron supplement indicated for use in improving the nutritional status of iron deficiency.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>188</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BIJUVA(estradiol and progesterone) Capsules</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
ammonium hydroxide, ethanol, ethyl acetate, FD&C Red #40, gelatin, glycerin, hydrolyzed gelatin, isopropyl alcohol, 
lauroyl polyoxyl-32 glycerides, lecithin, medium chain mono and di-glycerides, medium chain triglycerides, 
polyethylene glycol, polyvinyl acetate phthalate, propylene glycol, purified water, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Treatment Of Moderate To Severe Vasomotor Symptoms Due To Menopause.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>189</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BIKTARVY</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
croscarmellose sodium, magnesium stearate, and microcrystalline cellulose. The tablets are film-coated with 
a coating material containing iron oxide black, iron oxide red, polyethylene glycol, polyvinyl alcohol, talc, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BIKTARVY is indicated as a complete regimen for the treatment of human immunodeficiency virus type 1(HIV-1) 
infection in adults who have no antiretroviral treatment history
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>190</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BILTRICIDE (praziquantel)</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
corn starch, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose, povidone, sodium 
lauryl sulfate, polyethylene glycol, titanium dioxide and hypromellose.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BILTRICIDE® (praziquantel) is a trematodicide provided in tablet form for the oral treatment 
of schistosome infections and infections due to liver fluke.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>191</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Binimetinib</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
15 mg of binimetinib, lactose monohydrate, microcrystalline cellulose, croscarmellose sodium, 
magnesium stearate (vegetable source), and colloidal silicon dioxide,  polyvinyl alcohol, 
polyethylene glycol, titanium dioxide, talc, ferric oxide yellow, and ferrosoferric oxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Binimetinib is indicated for the treatment of patients with unresectable or metastatic melanoma 
with a BRAF V600E or V600K mutation, as detected by an FDA-approved test
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>192</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BINOSTO(alendronate sodium) Effervescent Tablets</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
91.37 mg of alendronate sodium, which is equivalent to 70 mg of free alendronic acid, 
monosodium citrate anhydrous, citric acid anhydrous, sodium hydrogen carbonate, and sodium 
carbonate anhydrous as buffering agents, strawberry flavor, acesulfame potassium, and sucralose.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BINOSTO is indicated for the treatment of osteoporosis in postmenopausal women. 
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>193</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BIOCLATE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
12.5 mg/mL Albumin (Human), 1.5 mg/mL polyethylene glycol (3350),180 mEq/L sodium, 55 mM histidine, 
1.5 pg/AHF International Unit (IU) polysorbate-80 and 0.20 mg/mL calcium. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BIOCLATE is indicated in hemophilia A (classical hemophilia) for the prevention and control of hemorrhagic episodes
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>194</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BIONECT® Cream</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Hyaluronic acid sodium salt (Hyalastine®), polyethyleneglycol 400 monostearate, decyl ester of oleic acid, emulsifying wax, 
glycerol, sorbitol solution 70%, sodium dehydroacetate, methylparaben, propylparaben, fragrance, purified water.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BIONECT® is indicated for the dressing and management of partial to full thickness dermal ulcers 
(pressure sores, venous stasis ulcers, arterial ulcers, diabetic ulcers), wounds including cuts, 
abrasions, donor sites, and post-operative incisions, irritations of the skin, and first and second degree burns.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>195</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BIOTHRAX</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
1.2 mg/mL aluminum, added as aluminum hydroxide in 0.85% sodium chloride, 25 mcg/mL 
benzethonium chloride and 100 mcg/mL formaldehyde, added as preservatives.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BioThrax is a vaccine indicated for the active immunization for the prevention of disease caused by 
Bacillus anthracis, in persons 18 through 65 years of age whose occupation or other activities place them at high risk of exposure.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>196</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Biperiden hydrochloride</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
2 mg biperiden hydrochloride,  corn syrup, lactose, magnesium stearate, potato starch and talc. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
As an adjunct in the therapy of all forms of parkinsonism (idiopathic, postencephalitic, arteriosclerotic)
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>197</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bismuth subcitrate</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Magnesium Stearate NF, Lactose Monohydrate NF, Talc USP, Gelatin USP, and Titanium Dioxide NF, Printed in red ink.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bismuth subcitrate are indicated for the treatment of patients with Helicobacter pylori infection and duodenal 
ulcer disease (active or history of within the past 5 years) to eradicate H. pylori.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>198</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bisoprolol fumarate</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Colloidal Silicon Dioxide, Corn Starch, Crospovidone, Dibasic Calcium Phosphate, Hypromellose, Magnesium Stearate, Microcrystalline 
Cellulose, Polyethylene Glycol, Polysorbate 80, and Titanium Dioxide. The 5 mg tablets also contain Red and Yellow Iron Oxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bisoprolol fumarate is indicated in the management of hypertension. It may be used alone or in combination with other antihypertensive agents.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>199</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bivalirudin</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
250 mg bivalirudin, equivalent to an average of 275 mg of bivalirudin trifluoroactetate*, 125 mg mannitol, 
and sodium hydroxide to adjust the pH to 5-6 (equivalent of approximately 12.5 mg sodium). 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bivalirudin is indicated for use as an anticoagulant in patients with unstable angina undergoing percutaneous transluminal coronary angioplasty (PTCA).
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>200</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BIVIGAM</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
10 mg/mL protein, of which not less than 96% is human immunoglobulin obtained from source human plasma. It is formulated in 
water for injection containing 0.100-0.140 M sodium chloride, 0.20-0.29 M glycine, 0.15 0.25% polysorbate 80, and pH 4.0 4.6.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BIVIGAM is an Immune Globulin Intravenous (Human), 10% Liquid, indicated for the treatment of patients with primary humoral immunodeficiency (PI).
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>201</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BLEPH-10</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
sulfacetamide sodium 10% (100 mg/mL),  benzalkonium chloride 0.005%, edetate disodium; polysorbate 80; polyvinyl alcohol 1.4%; purified water; 
sodium phosphate dibasic; sodium phosphate monobasic; sodium thiosulfate; hydrochloric acid and/or sodium hydroxide to adjust the pH (6.8 to 7.5).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BLEPH-10 (sulfacetamide sodium ophthalmic solution 10%) solution is indicated for the treatment of conjunctivitis and other 
superficial ocular infections due to susceptible microorganisms, and as an adjunctive in systemic sulfonamide therapy of trachoma.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>202</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BLEPHAMIDE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
sulfacetamide sodium 10%, prednisolone acetate (microfine suspension) 0.2%,  benzalkonium chloride (0.004%); edetate disodium; 
polysorbate 80; polyvinyl alcohol 1.4%; potassium phosphate, monobasic; purified water; sodium phosphate, dibasic; 
sodium thiosulfate; hydrochloric acid and/or sodium hydroxide to adjust pH (6.6 to 7.2).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BLEPHAMIDE® ophthalmic suspension is a steroid/anti-infective combination drug indicated for 
steroid-responsive inflammatory ocular conditions for which a corticosteroid is indicated and 
where superficial bacterial ocular infection or a risk of bacterial ocular infection exists.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>203</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Blinatumomab</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
citric acid monohydrate (52.5 mg), lysine hydrochloride (2283.8 mg), polysorbate 80 (10 mg), 
sodium hydroxide to adjust pH to 7.0, and water for injection.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Blinatumomab is indicated for the treatment of B-cell precursor acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) in first 
or second complete remission with minimal residual disease (MRD) greater than or equal to 0.1% in adults and children.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>204</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BLINCYTO</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
citric acid monohydrate (52.5 mg), lysine hydrochloride (2283.8 mg), polysorbate 80 (10 mg), 
sodium hydroxide to adjust pH to 7.0, and water for injection
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BLINCYTO is indicated for the treatment of B-cell precursor acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) in first 
or second complete remission with minimal residual disease (MRD) greater than or equal to 0.1% in adults and children.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>205</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BLOCADREN</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
10 mg or 20 mg timolol maleate for oral administration. Inactive ingredients are cellulose, FD&C Blue 2, magnesium stearate, and starch.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BLOCADREN (timolol) is indicated for the treatment of hypertension. It may be used alone or in 
combination with other antihypertensive agents, especially thiazide-type diuretics.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>206</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BLOXIVERZ</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
neostigmine methylsulfate 1 mg, phenol 4.5 mg (used as preservative), and sodium acetate trihydrate 0.2 mg, in water for injection
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BLOXIVERZ is a cholinesterase inhibitor indicated for the reversal of the effects of 
non-depolarizing neuromuscular blocking agents after surgery.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>207</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Boceprevir Capsules</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
sodium lauryl sulfate, microcrystalline cellulose, lactose monohydrate, 
croscarmellose sodium, pre-gelatinized starch, and magnesium stearate,  
gelatin, titanium dioxide, D&C Yellow #10, FD&C Blue #1, and FD&C Red #40. 
The yellow capsule body contains gelatin, titanium dioxide, D&C Yellow #10, 
FD&C Red #40, and FD&C Yellow #6. The capsule is printed with red and yellow ink. 
The red ink contains shellac and red iron oxide, while the yellow ink 
consists of shellac, titanium dioxide, povidone and D&C Yellow #10 Aluminum Lake. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
boceprevir is indicated for the treatment of chronic hepatitis C genotype 1 infection, 
in combination with peginterferon alfa and ribavirin, in adult patients with compensated 
liver disease, including cirrhosis, who are previously untreated or who have failed previous 
interferon and ribavirin therapy, including prior null responders, partial responders, and relapsers 
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>208</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BONIVA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
lactose monohydrate, povidone, microcrystalline cellulose, crospovidone, purified stearic acid, colloidal 
silicon dioxide, and purified water, hypromellose, titanium dioxide, talc, polyethylene glycol 6000, and purified water.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BONIVA is indicated for the treatment and prevention of osteoporosis in postmenopausal women. BONIVA increases 
bone mineral density (BMD) and reduces the incidence of vertebral fractures.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>209</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BONTRIL PDM</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Compressible Sugar, Confectioner's Sugar, D&C Yellow #10, FD&C Blue #1, FD&C Yellow #6, Isopropyl Alcohol, Lactose 
Anhydrous, Magnesium Stearate, Microcrystalline Cellulose, Povidone, Purified Water, Sodium Starch Glycolate.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bontril PDM (phendimetrazine tartrate) is indicatedin the management of exogenous obesity as a short term adjunct 
(a few weeks) in a regimen of weight reduction based on caloric restriction in patients with an initial body mass 
index (BMI) of 30 kg/m2 or higher who have not responded to appropriate weight reducing regimen (diet and/or exercise) alone.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>210</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BOOSTRIX</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
aluminum hydroxide as adjuvant (not more than 0.39 mg aluminum by assay), 4.5 mg of sodium chloride, 
< 100 mcg of residual formaldehyde, and ≤ 100 mcg of polysorbate 80 (Tween 80), natural rubber latex.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BOOSTRIX is indicated for active booster immunization against tetanus, diphtheria, and pertussis. 
BOOSTRIX is approved for use as a single dose in individuals 10 years of age and older.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>211</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bortezomib</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
35 mg mannitol, USP, mannitol ester in equilibrium with its hydrolysis product, the monomeric boronic acid. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bortezomib is indicated for the treatment of patients with multiple myeloma.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>212</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bosentan</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
corn starch, pregelatinized starch, sodium starch glycolate, povidone, glyceryl behenate, magnesium stearate, 
hydroxypropylmethylcellulose, triacetin, talc, titanium dioxide, iron oxide yellow, iron oxide red, and ethylcellulose.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bosentan is indicated for the treatment of pulmonary arterial hypertension 
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>213</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BOSULIF</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
microcrystalline cellulose, croscarmellose sodium, poloxamer, povidone, magnesium 
stearate, polyvinyl alcohol, titanium dioxide, polyethylene glycol, talc, and iron 
oxide yellow (for 100 mg, and 400 mg tablet) and iron oxide red (for 400 mg, and 500 mg tablet).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BOSULIF is indicated for the treatment of adult patients with newly-diagnosed chronic 
phase (CP) Philadelphia chromosome-positive chronic myelogenous leukemia (Ph+ CML). 
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>214</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BOTOX</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
50 Units of Clostridium botulinum type A neurotoxin complex, 0.25 mg of Albumin Human, and 0.45 mg of 
sodium chloride; 100 Units of Clostridium botulinum type A neurotoxin complex, 0.5 mg of Albumin Human, 
and 0.9 mg of sodium chloride; or 200 Units of Clostridium botulinum type A neurotoxin complex, 1 mg of 
Albumin Human, and 1.8 mg of sodium chloride in a sterile, vacuum-dried form without a preservative.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BOTOX (onabotulinumtoxinA) for injection is indicated for the treatment of overactive bladder 
with symptoms of urge urinary incontinence, urgency, and frequency, in adults who have an 
inadequate response to or are intolerant of an anticholinergic me dication.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>215</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Botulinum toxin type b</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
5,000 Units of botulinum toxin type B per milliliter in 0.05% human serum 
albumin, 0.01 M sodium succinate, and 0.1 M sodium chloride at approximately pH 5.6.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Botulinum toxin type b is indicated for the treatment of adults with cervical dystonia to 
reduce the severity of abnormal head position and neck pain associated with cervical dystonia.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO> 216</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRAFTOVI</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
copovidone, poloxamer 188, microcrystalline cellulose, succinic acid, crospovidone, colloidal silicon 
dioxide, magnesium stearate (vegetable origin), gelatin, titanium dioxide, iron oxide red, iron oxide 
yellow, ferrosoferric oxide, monogramming ink (pharmaceutical glaze, ferrosoferric oxide, propylene glycol).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BRAFTOVI is indicated, in combination with binimetinib, for the treatment of patients with unresectable or 
metastatic melanoma with a BRAF V600E or V600K mutation, as detected by an FDA-approved test 
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>217</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRAVELLE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
23 mg Lactose Monohydrate, 0.005 mg Polysorbate 20, and Sodium Phosphate buffer 
 (Sodium Phosphate dibasic, Heptahydrate and Phosphoric acid)
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BRAVELLE is a product containing a highly purified preparation of human follicle 
stimulating hormone (hFSH) extracted from the urine of postmenopausal women
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>218</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Brentuximab vedotin</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
70 mg/mL trehalose dihydrate, 5.6 mg/mL sodium citrate dihydrate, 0.21 mg/mL 
citric acid monohydrate, and 0.20 mg/mL polysorbate 80 and water for injection.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Brentuximab vedotin is indicated for the treatment of adult patients with previously 
untreated Stage III or IV cHL, in combination with doxorubicin, vinblastine, and dacarbazine.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>219</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BREO ELLIPTA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
a white powder mix of micronized fluticasone furoate (100 or 200 mcg) and lactose 
monohydrate (12.4 mg), and each blister on the other strip contains a white powder 
mix of micronized vilanterol trifenatate (40 mcg equivalent to 25 mcg of vilanterol), 
magnesium stearate (125 mcg), and lactose monohydrate (12.34 mg), milk proteins.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BREO ELLIPTA is indicated for the long-term, once-daily, maintenance treatment of airflow 
obstruction in patients with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>220</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Brevicon</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
D&C Green No. 5, D&C Yellow No. 10, lactose, povidone, and starch,  FD&C Yellow No. 6, 
microcrystalline cellulose, and magnesium stearate, norethindrone 0.5 mg and ethinyl estradiol 0.035 mg.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Brevicon are indicated for the prevention of pregnancy in women who 
elect to use this product as a method of contraception.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>221</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Brevoxyl-4 Gel</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
benzoyl peroxide 4% and 8%, respectively, as the active Ingredient In a gel 
vehicle containing purified water, cetyl alcohol, dimethyl Isosorblde, 
fragrance, simethicone, stearyl alcohol and ceteareth-20.
<TEXT>
Brevoxyl-4 Gel (benzoyl peroxide gel) and Brevoxyl-8 Gel are indicated 
for use in the topical treatment of mild to moderate acne vulgaris.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>222</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Brexpiprazole</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
lactose monohydrate, corn starch, microcrystalline cellulose, hydroxypropyl 
cellulose, lowsubstituted hydroxypropyl cellulose, magnesium stearate, 
hypromellose, and talc, titanium dioxide, iron oxide and ferrosferric oxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Brexpiprazole is indicated for Adjunctive treatment of major depressive disorder (MDD) 
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>223</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRIDION</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
100 mg sugammadex, which is equivalent to 108.8 mg sugammadex sodium.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BRIDION is indicated for the reversal of neuromuscular blockade induced by 
rocuronium bromide and vecuronium bromide in adults undergoing surgery.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>224</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Brigatinib</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
lactose monohydrate, microcrystalline cellulose, sodium starch glycolate 
(Type A), magnesium stearate, and hydrophobic colloidal silica, talc, 
 polyethylene glycol, polyvinyl alcohol, and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Brigatinib is indicated for the treatment of patients with anaplastic 
lymphoma kinase (ALK)-positive metastatic non-small cell lung cancer 
(NSCLC) who have progressed on or are intolerant to crizotinib.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>225</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRILINTA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
mannitol, dibasic calcium phosphate, sodium starch glycolate, hydroxypropyl cellulose, 
magnesium stearate, hydroxypropyl methylcellulose, titanium dioxide, talc, polyethylene glycol 400, and ferric oxide yellow.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BRILINTA is indicated to reduce the rate of cardiovascular death, myocardial infarction, and stroke in patients with acute 
coronary syndrome (ACS) or a history of myocardial infarction (MI). For at least the first 12 months following ACS, it is superior to clopidogrel.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>227</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Brimonidine tartrate</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
sodium carboxymethylcellulose; sodium borate; boric acid; sodium chloride; potassium chloride; calcium chloride; magnesium chloride; 
PURITE® 0.005% (0.05 mg/mL) as a preservative; purified water; and hydrochloric acid and/or sodium hydroxide
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Brimonidine tartrate is an alpha adrenergic receptor agonist indicated for the reduction of elevated 
intraocular pressure (IOP) in patients with open-angle glaucoma or ocular hypertension.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>228</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRINEURA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
calcium chloride dihydrate (1.05 mg); magnesium chloride hexahydrate (0.8 mg); potassium chloride (1.1 mg); sodium chloride 
(43.85 mg); sodium phosphate, dibasic, heptahydrate (0.55 mg); sodium phosphate, monobasic, monohydrate (0.4 mg); and Water for Injection, USP.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Brineura is indicated to slow the loss of ambulation in symptomatic pediatric patients 3 years of age and older with late 
infantile neuronal ceroid lipofuscinosis type 2 (CLN2), also known as tripeptidyl peptidase 1 (TPP1) deficiency.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>229</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRINTELLIX</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
mannitol, microcrystalline cellulose, hydroxypropyl cellulose, sodium starch glycolate, magnesium stearate 
and film coating which consists of hypromellose, titanium dioxide, polyethylene glycol 400, iron oxide red 
(5 mg, 15 mg, and 20 mg) and iron oxide yellow (10 mg and 15 mg).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BRINTELLIX is indicated for the treatment of major depressive disorder (MDD). The efficacy of BRINTELLIX 
was established in six 6 to 8 week studies (including one study in the elderly) and one maintenance study in adults
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>230</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Brinzolamide</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
Benzalkonium chloride 0.1 m, mannitol, carbomer 974P, tyloxapol, edetate disodium, 
sodium chloride, purified water, with hydrochloric acid and/or sodium hydroxide
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Brinzolamide is a carbonic anhydrase inhibitor indicated in the treatment of elevated 
intraocular pressure in patients with ocular hypertension or open-angle glaucoma.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>231</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRISDELLE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
dibasic calcium phosphate, sodium starch glycolate, magnesium stearate, gelatin, 
titanium dioxide, FD&C Yellow #6, FD&C Red #3, FD&C Red #40, shellac, and black iron oxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BRISDELLE is indicated for the treatment of moderate to severe 
vasomotor symptoms (VMS) associated with menopause.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>232</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRIVIACT</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
croscarmellose sodium, lactose monohydrate, betadex (β]-cyclodextrin), anhydrous lactose, magnesium 
stearate, and film coating agents, polyvinyl alcohol, talc, polyethylene glycol 3350, titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BRIVIACT injection is a clear, colorless liquid provided as a sterile, preservative-free solution.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>233</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bromday</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
boric acid, disodium edetate (0.2 mg/mL), polysorbate 80 (1.5 mg/mL), povidone (20 mg/mL), sodium borate, 
sodium sulfite anhydrous (2 mg/mL), sodium hydroxide to adjust pH and water for injection, USP.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bromday is indicated for the treatment of postoperative inflammation and reduction of 
ocular pain in patients who have undergone cataract surgery.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>234</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bromfenac</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
benzalkonium chloride (0.05 mg/mL), boric acid, disodium edetate (0.2 mg/mL), polysorbate 
80 (1.5 mg/mL), povidone (20 mg/mL), sodium borate, sodium sulfite anhydrous (2 mg/mL), 
sodium hydroxide to adjust pH and water for injection, USP.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bromfenac ophthalmic solution 0.09% is indicated for the treatment of postoperative 
inflammation and reduction of ocular pain in patients who have undergone cataract surgery.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>235</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bromocriptine mesylate</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
colloidal silicon dioxide, gelatin, lactose, magnesium stearate, red iron oxide, 
silicon dioxide, sodium lauryl sulfate, starch, titanium dioxide, yellow iron oxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bromocriptine mesylate is indicated for the treatment of dysfunctions associated with hyperprolactinemia 
including amenorrhea with or without galactorrhea, infertility or hypogonadism.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>236</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BROMSITE</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
boric acid, sodium borate, citric acid anhydrous, sodium citrate dihydrate, 
poloxamer 407, polycarbophil, sodium chloride, edetate disodium dihydrate, 
sodium hydroxide (to adjust pH to 8.3), and water for injection (USP).
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BromSite is indicated for the treatment of postoperative inflammation and 
prevention of ocular pain in patients undergoing cataract surgery.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>237</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BROVANA</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
15 mcg of arformoterol (equivalent to 22 mcg of arformoterol tartrate) in a sterile, 
isotonic saline solution, pH-adjusted to 5.0 with citric acid and sodium citrate.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BROVANA (arformoterol tartrate) Inhalation Solution is indicated for the long-term, 
twice daily (morning and evening) maintenance treatment of bronchoconstriction in patients 
with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD), including chronic bronchitis and emphysema.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>238</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BRYHALI</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
0.1 mg (0.01%) halobetasol propionate in a white to off-white lotion base consisting of carbomer copolymer 
type B, carbomer homopolymer type A, diethyl sebacate, edetate disodium dihydrate, light mineral oil, 
methylparaben, propylparaben, purified water, sodium hydroxide, sorbitan monooleate and sorbitol solution, 70%.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BRYHALI (halobetasol propionate) lotion, 0.01% is indicated for the topical treatment of plaque psoriasis in adults
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>239</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BSS PLUS</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
sodium chloride 7.44 mg, potassium chloride 0.395 mg, dibasic sodium phosphate 0.433 mg, sodium bicarbonate 
2.19 mg, hydrochloric acid and/or sodium hydroxide, calcium chloride dihydrate 3.85 mg, magnesium chloride 
hexahydrate 5 mg, dextrose 23 mg, glutathione disulfide (oxidized glutathione) 4.6 mg.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BSS PLUS is indicated for use as an intraocular irrigating solution during intraocular 
surgical procedures involving perfusion of the eye.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>240</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BUDEPRION XL</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
ethyl alcohol, ethylcellulose, hydrochloric acid, hydroxypropylcellulose, methacrylic acid 
copolymer, povidone, silicon dioxide, and hydrogenated vegetable oil. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUDEPRION XL (bupropion hydrochloride extended-release tablets) is indicated for the treatment 
of major depressive disorder.
</TEXT>



 240

</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>241</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BUMEX</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
anhydrous lactose, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose, pregelatinized 
starch, talc, 0.5 mg-D&C Yellow No. 10 aluminum lake and FD&C Blue No. 1 aluminum 
lake; 1 mg-D&C Yellow No. 10 aluminum lake; 2 mg- red iron oxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bumex tablets are indicated for the treatment of edema associated with congestive 
heart failure, hepatic and renal disease, including the nephrotic syndrome.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>242</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BUNAVAIL</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
buprenorphine HCl, a mu-opioid receptor partial agonist and a kappa-opioid 
receptor antagonist, and naloxone HCl dihydrate, an opioid receptor 
antagonist, at a ratio of ~6:1 (ratio of free bases)
delayed
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUNAVAIL is indicated for the treatment of opioid dependence. BUNAVAIL should be used 
as part of a complete treatment plan that includes counseling and psychosocial support.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>243</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bupap</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
colloidal silicon dioxide, croscarmellose sodium, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline 
cellulose with capsule shell composed of gelatin (silicon dioxide and sodium lauryl 
sulfate added as manufacturing aides to the gelatin) and titanium dioxide.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Bupap are indicated for the relief of the symptom complex of tension (or muscle contraction) headache.
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>244</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BUPHENYL</PROFILE>


<HEADLINE>
500 mg of sodium phenylbutyrate, microcrystalline cellulose NF, magnesium 
stearate NF,  0.94 grams of sodium phenylbutyrate and the inactive 
ingredients calcium stearate NF, and colloidal silicon dioxide NF.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUPHENYL is indicated as adjunctive therapy in the chronic management of patients 
with urea cycle disorders involving deficiencies of carbamylphosphate synthetase (CPS), 
ornithine transcarbamylase (OTC), or argininosuccinic acid synthetase (AS).
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>245</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Buprenex</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
BUPHENYL is indicated as adjunctive therapy in the chronic management of patients with urea cycle 
disorders involving deficiencies of carbamylphosphate synthetase (CPS), ornithine transcarbamylase 
(OTC), or argininosuccinic acid synthetase (AS). 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUPHENYL is indicated as adjunctive therapy in the chronic management of patients with urea cycle 
disorders involving deficiencies of carbamylphosphate synthetase (CPS), ornithine transcarbamylase 
(OTC), or argininosuccinic acid synthetase (AS). 
</TEXT>
</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>246</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bupropion hydrochloride</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
carnauba wax, cysteine hydrochloride, hypromellose, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose, 
polyethylene glycol, polysorbate 80, and titanium dioxide and is printed with edible black ink.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUPHENYL is indicated as adjunctive therapy in the chronic management of patients with urea cycle disorders 
involving deficiencies of carbamylphosphate synthetase (CPS), ornithine transcarbamylase (OTC), or argininosuccinic acid synthetase (AS). 
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>247</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BUSPAR</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
colloidal silicon dioxide, lactose monohydrate, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose and sodium starch glycolate. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUSPAR are indicated for the management of anxiety disorders or the short-term relief of the symptoms of anxiety. 
Anxiety or tension associated with the stress of everyday life usually does not require treatment with an anxiolytic.
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>248</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Bupropion hydrochloride</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
 carnauba wax, cysteine hydrochloride, hypromellose, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose, 
 polyethylene glycol, polysorbate 80, and titanium dioxide and is printed with edible black ink.
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUPHENYL is indicated as adjunctive therapy in the chronic management of patients with urea cycle disorders involving 
 of carbamylphosphate synthetase (CPS), ornithine transcarbamylase (OTC), or argininosuccinic acid synthetase (AS). 
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>249</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BUSPAR</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
colloidal silicon dioxide, lactose monohydrate, magnesium stearate, microcrystalline cellulose and sodium starch glycolate. 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUSPAR are indicated for the management of anxiety disorders or the short-term relief of the symptoms of anxiety. 
Anxiety or tension associated with the stress of everyday life usually does not require treatment with an anxiolytic. 
</TEXT>
</DOC>

<DOC>
<DOCNO>250</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>BUTISOL SODIUM</PROFILE>
<HEADLINE>
calcium stearate, corn starch, dibasic calcium phosphate, FD&C Blue No. 1 (30 mg only), 
FD&C Yellow No. 5 (30 mg and 50 mg — see PRECAUTIONS), FD&C Yellow No. 6 (50 mg only). 
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
BUTISOL SODIUM is indicated for use as a sedative or hypnotic. 
</TEXT>
</DOC>

</DOCS>
</NEWS>