<NEWS>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>1</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Dacarbazine(Dtic - FDA Dome)</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
100 mg of dacarbazine, or 700 mg of dacarbazine (the active ingredient), anhydrous citric acid and mannitol
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
DTlC-Dome is indicated in the treatment of metastatic malignant melanoma. In addition, DTlC-Dome is also indicated for Hodgkin's disease as a second-line therapy when used in combination with other effective agents.ns.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 7 Photograph (Omitted).
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>2</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Dabigatran Etexila -FDA Mesylate (Pradaxa)
</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
75, 110, and 150 mg strengths for oral administration, 172.95 mg dabigatran etexilate mesylate (equivalent to 150 mg dabigatran etexilate), 126.83 mg dabigatran etexilate mesylate (equivalent to 110 mg dabigatran etexilate), or 86.48 mg dabigatran etexilate mesylate (equivalent to 75 mg dabigatran etexilate)

</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By KENNETH GOODING, Mining Correspondent
</BYLINE>
<TEXT>
Dabigatran keeps your blood from coagulating (clotting) to prevent unwanted blood clots, this medicine can also make it easier for you to bleed, even from a minor injury such as a fall or a bump on the head.  tablets are a combination of two nucleoside analogues (abacavir and lamivudine). KIVEXA is indicated in antiretroviral combination therapy for the treatment of Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV) infection in adults and adolescents from 12 years of age.

</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 22
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>3</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Dapsone Tablets USP
</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
100 mg/day and higher trimethoprim dose, 20 mg/kg/day, demonstrated that the serum levels of dapsone were increased by 40% and trimethoprim levels were increased by 48% when the drugs were administered concurrently.

</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By DAVID GOODHART
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   BONN
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
Dapsone has been found carcinogenic (sarcomagenic) for male rats and female mice causing mesenchymal tumors in the spleen and peritoneum, and thyroid carcinoma in female rats. 

</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 20
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>4</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Diatrizoate meglumine and iodipamide meglumine Injection
</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
 527 mg diatrizoate meglumine and 268 mg iodipamide meglumine with 3.2 mg sodium citrate as a buffer, and 0.4 mg edetate disodium; pH has been adjusted to 7.0 to 7.8 with meglumine and diatrizoic acid. 

</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Diatrizoate Meglumine and lodipamide Meglumine Injection is indicated for use in hysterosalpingography.

</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 1
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>5</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Diazepam Injection, Solution 5 mg/mL, Ampul, Fliptop Vial
</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
5 mg diazepam; 40% propylene glycol; 10% alcohol; 5% sodium benzoate and benzoic acid added as buffers; and 1.5% benzyl alcohol added as a preservative. pH 6.6 (6.2 to 6.9).

</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Diazepam tablets, USP are indicated for the management of anxiety disorders or for the short-term relief of the symptoms of anxiety. 

</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 1
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>6</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BEOA7AAFFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / World News in Brief: Khmer Rouge snub
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Khmer Rouge guerrillas refused a UN observer team's request for a visit to
the front line to observe the Cambodian ceasefire.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 1
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>7</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BEOA7AAEFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / World News in Brief: Cocaine ring broken
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Spanish police said they had broken up a cocaine-smuggling ring, arresting
15 Chileans and seizing Pta92m (Dollars 900,000) in cash.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 1
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>8</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BEOA7AADFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / World News in Brief: Malawi frees poet
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Malawi has freed dissident poet Jack Mapanje, 46, detained without trial for
more than three years, Amnesty International said.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 1
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>9</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BEOA7AACFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / World News in Brief: Booby-trap murder
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
A Northern Ireland businessman and senior member of the loyalist Orange
Order died when an IRA bomb exploded under his car in Armagh.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 1
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>10</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BEOA7AABFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / World News in Brief: Brussels rioting
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Almost 200 North African immigrants were arrested in Brussels at the weekend
during the worst racial rioting ever seen in the normally placid Belgian
capital.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 1
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>11</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BEOA7AAAFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / World News in Brief: Soviet deadlock
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
The Soviet parliament was deadlocked over a bill to guarantee the right to
travel abroad. Many deputies suggested authorities could not cope with a
flood of tourists and would-be emigrants.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
International Page 1
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>12</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAGGFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / London Stock Exchange: FT-SE 2,500 lost in nervous trading
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
FRESH indications of the depth of the UK recession, wavering optimism for
base rate cuts this week and a poor lead from Wall Street all combined to
undermine the UK stock market yesterday.
Pressure for a further reduction in base rates was increased by the news
yesterday that the monthly rise in domestic consumer borrowing was at a
six-year low in March. However, last week's cautionary views on interest
rates from the Bank of England have cast uncertainty over hopes in the City
of London that UK base rates will be cut this Friday in the wake of the
expected fall in the UK retail price index.
Attempts by the equity market to hold on to FT-SE 2,500, reached at the end
of last month, proved fruitless yesterday and the market closed 37.7 points
down at 2,486.6. The final picture was exceedingly gloomy, with the London
market extending its losses to finish virtually at the day's low as Wall
Street continued its overnight fall of 51 Dow points by losing a further
9.39 early in the new session.
Confidence was not helped at the close by sudden rumours that another large
rights issue is in the offing. Institutional coffers are beginning to feel
the weight of a 1991 rights issue burden already approaching Pounds 4bn,
without including a substantial number of share placings.
In the face of Wall Street's heavy setback on Friday night, the London
market opened 23 Footsie points off, quickly abandoning the FT-SE 2,500 mark
attained at the close of business on April 30. There was no significant
recovery during the session but further losses were restrained at first by
the relative absence of sellers and a FT-SE June futures contract which
managed to hold above 2,500 until late in the day. But losses in share
prices were rapidly extended in late trading as the big institutions backed
away from the stock market.
Market volume, as recorded by a Seaq-traded shares total of 354.9m shares,
was low, even by comparison with Friday's 423m figure. The institutions were
believed to be top slicing, selling a small part of their holdings in blue
chip stocks in the expectation that these shares will be bought back more
cheaply in the weeks ahead.
Weakness in oil shares set the trend for widespread losses among Wall
Street-orientated stocks. The industrial blue chips featured falls in BOC,
BAT Industries, Reuters and ICI. However, share losses in the international
sector were mostly suffered early in the session and did not increase
disproportionately after Wall Street opened lower; some analysts commented
that this indicated that domestic factors were the most significant in the
market yesterday.
The uncertain political scene in the UK, ahead of Thursday's by-election in
the Monmouth constituency acted as a further discouragement to the big
institutions, which are increasingly of the view that there will be little
to attract them to the UK stock market until the third quarter of the year.
Trading specialists suggested yesterday that, with their cash holdings
drained by rights issues, the institutions are now less willing to buy cheap
stock whenever the market gives ground. Some believe that fund managers may
wait until the FT-SE falls by a further 50 or more points before making
serious buying forays.
However, optimism for a further strong rise in the UK market over the next
12 months, perhaps to around FT-SE 2,750, remains undimmed.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 40
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>13</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAGFFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / London Stock Exchange: Equity Futures and Options Trading
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
LONDON derivatives continued to trade under the shadow of Wall Street,
opening weaker following the decline in the US in the previous session and
then slipping still lower as New York extended its slide in London hours
yesterday.
The UK equity futures market began weakly and helped to pull the stock
market down. The premium of the June FT-SE 100 index over the spot index
narrowed from 20 points to around 10 on selling by independent traders.
At one stage, the futures market attempted to rally and succeeded in
widening the gap over the share market to 20 points. But with Wall Street on
the defensive, prices were again marked lower and by the close June was back
to less than a 10-point premium to the spot market.
The June FT-SE closed at 2,494, down 42 points on the day. Its premium
finished at 6 points, against fair value of 15.
In traded options, the stock market's inability to break out of the range of
the past fortnight prompted investors to sell calls against stock holdings.
Elsewhere, there was a buyer of 1,000 Asda July 130 calls; a buyer of 500
GrandMet October 650 puts; and a buyer of 250 Barclays June 460 calls.
The Euro FT-SE was boosted by a seller of 1,000 July 2,625 calls and a buyer
of 1,000 July 2,525 puts.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 40
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>14</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAGEFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / World Stock Markets (America): Bond recovery fails to bring
joy to equities
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By PATRICK HARVERSON
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   NEW YORK
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
Wall Street
THE STOCK market remained subdued yesterday in the wake of last Friday's
sell-off, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average rallying only marginally in
very light trading from the 50-point drop, writes Patrick Harverson in New
York.
At the close the Dow was 4.25 up at 2,924.42, having spent most of the day
in negative territory. The more broadly based Standard &amp; Poor's 500 moved in
similar fashion, recovering 1.02 on balance at 376.76, while the Nasdaq
composite picked up 0.51 to 493.93. Turnover on the New York SE totalled
just 130m shares, while rises showed a small lead over falls at the finish
by 786 to 742.
On Friday it was the sharp fall in bond values which led share prices lower,
but yesterday's modest recovery in the bond market failed to stimulate a
similar movement among stocks. The weakness in the US economy continues to
trouble investors, who can see little reason to invest more of their money
in equities.
Yesterday's industrial production data provided no real comfort on the
economic front. Although the data showed an expected 0.1 per cent increase
in April production, the Federal Reserve also revealed a revised 0.6 per
cent decline in March production, previously estimated at 0.3 per cent.
Banks featured, with American Express dropping Dollars 1 1/4 to Dollars 22
3/4 on turnover of 4.1m shares after announcing that it would take a Dollars
144m pre-tax charge to account for the 28 per cent stake held by Shearson
Lehman Brothers, its securities subsidiary, in First Capital Holdings, the
troubled Californian life insurance group.
Bankers Trust was down Dollars 1 at Dollars 48 5/8 after the New York-based
banking group confirmed it was laying off 200 staff, while JP Morgan, which
had been actively bought since it was announced over a week ago that the
stock would join the Dow index, slipped Dollars 1 1/2 to Dollars 50 3/8 on
meeting profit-taking.
Square D jumped Dollars 6 3/8 to Dollars 87 3/8 after the company agreed to
the bid by Schneider, of France, of Dollars 88 a share, or Dollars 2.23bn.
AT&amp;T bucked the trend, firming Dollars  5/8 to Dollars 36 1/2 in active
trading after reports that the merger with NCR is proceeding faster than
expected.
On the over-the-counter market, Nordstrom jumped Dollars 2 3/4 to Dollars 44
on turnover of 1.5m shares on the back of an improvement of almost 100 per
cent in first-quarter profits. Apple Computer climbed Dollars 1 1/2 to
Dollars 52 3/4 on volume of 2.2m shares after the company introduced its
System 7 operating system software and said it would cut prices on logic
board upgrades and memory kits for the Macintosh.
Metcalf &amp; Eddy fell Dollars 1 1/2 to Dollars 15 1/4 after the water
treatment and waste management company issued a second-quarter profits
warning.
Canada
AFTER spending most of the day in lower territory, the Toronto market
managed a mild recovery during the afternoon to end on a mixed note.
The composite index was finally a net 2.9 up at 3,492.7 but declining issues
still held an edge over advances by 273 to 240. Volume amounted to 21.6m
shares, down from Friday's 23.3m.
Lincoln Waste Management topped the most actives list after one of the
company's largest shareholders and one of its directors sold more than 4m
shares, approaching one-fifth of the session's moderate volume. The share
price was steady at CDollars 10 7/8 .
John Labatt, which rose CDollars 1 to CDollars 23 5/8 , said it is
considering selling its JL Foods Inc unit.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 37
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>15</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAGDFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / Foreign Exchanges: Dollar and yen lose ground
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
THE DOLLAR fell against European currencies but improved in terms of the
Japanese yen yesterday. A rise of 0.1 per cent in April US industrial
production was roughly in line with expectations, while a revised fall of
0.6 per cent from 0.3 per cent in March output brought little reaction in
the US currency.
A decline to 78.3 per cent in April US capacity utilisation, from a downward
revision to 78.5 per cent for March, also had no effect on a market waiting
for today's data on US consumer prices and Friday's trade figures.
At the London close the dollar had fallen to DM1.7140 from DM1.7255; to
FFr5.8050 from FFr5.8400; and to SFr1.4430 from SFr1.4580. On the other hand
it rose to Y139.40 from Y138.75 against a generally weak yen. The dollar's
index dipped to 66.2 from 66.4.
Speculation about an early cut in the Bank of Japan's discount rate
depressed the yen. This helped to boost the D-Mark after rumours subsided
that Mr Karl Otto Pohl was about to resign as president of the German
Bundesbank.
The rumours led to D-Mark nervousness in early trading, but by the end of
the day attention was focused on interest rate factors and this pushed the
German currency up against the yen. It finished in London at Y81.35 compared
with Y80.40 on Friday.
In the European exchange rate mechanism the D-Mark improved against the
weakest placed French franc and also the Italian lira, but lost ground to
sterling.
The Bank of France left its money market intervention rate unchanged at 9
per cent at a securities repurchase tender, keeping interest rate
differentials steady as the Bank of Spain and Belgian National Bank also
left rates unaltered at similar tenders.
The lira weakened against several of its partners in the ERM after Sunday's
one-point cut to 11 1/2 per cent in the Bank of Italy's discount rate.
However, it remained the second strongest ERM currency, according to figures
from the European Commission, in spite of losing ground to the D-Mark,
French franc and other members of the ERM at the Milan fixing.
Sterling was the third strongest ERM currency as speculation continued about
the possible timing of another reduction in UK bank base rates. Mr David
Mellor, chief secretary to the Treasury, said on BBC radio that 'the
chancellor will not cut interest rates until he considers it prudent to do
so'.
The Bank of England has signalled that it does not consider this an
appropriate time, but the market still believes an early cut is possible as
political pressure increases on the government.
Sterling rose 1.30 cents to Dollars 1.7320, while improving to DM2.9675 from
DM2.9650; to Y241.50 from Y238.50; and to FFr10.0550 from FFr10.0400, but it
eased to SFr2.5000 from SFr2.5075. The pound's index put on 0.2 to 91.8.
Sterling gained a further 20 points in New York to end at Dollars 1.7340.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 31
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>16</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAGCFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / Commodities and Agriculture: Farmers' Viewpoint - Machinery
rings seem an all-round success story / The time is coming in the UK for a
co-operative idea already working very well on the Continent
</HEADLINE>
<TEXT>
Farmers love government grants. But the flurry of urgent activity in recent
weeks to beat today's deadline for applications for grant aid to help set up
machinery rings has been out of all proportion to their value. There are
much more significant reasons for farmers to co-operate in an effort to cut
the capital costs of machinery. The ending of the modest Pounds 10,000 per
ring grant payable over three years merely concentrated minds.
Machinery rings began in Germany about 25 years ago. Born out of hard times,
they brought together groups of farmers in local areas who were prepared to
work some of their machinery on other people's farms where the appropriate
tackle was worn out or did not exist. In other words, one member of a ring
might provide the combine harvester and deal with the grain on a number of
farms while another would bale the straw and yet another might plough and
plant all the land for the following year's crops.
Rings formalised local arrangements of this kind which had been going on
between farmers in the same village for years and set standard charges for
given tasks. By broadening the area over which such arrangements operated,
it also gave members access to more specialised equipment. By employing a
manager to co-ordinate the work it provided organisation and a guarantee of
payment to those who did the work.
Today, there are about 260 machinery rings in Germany and the idea has
spread to other European countries, especially Holland and France. There
were no rings established in the UK, however, until 1987 after a visit to
Germany by a Scottish agricultural adviser who came home and enthused his
clients over the concept. Since then, 10 machinery rings have been set up in
Scotland.
Although most are still developing and expanding, it is expected that the
total turnover of the Scottish rings this year will reach Pounds 2.5m.
Moreover, the single most successful Scottish group, with 220 members
already, has a turnover in excess of Pounds 1m.
The first English machinery ring was formed in Sussex and Kent only last
year. Since then, 15 more have been established across the country. All have
or are hoping to qualify for the Pounds 10,000 grant, 25 per cent of which
comes from the EC and 75 per cent from the UK government. The scheme is
administered by Food From Britain. At least another two rings are thought to
be in course of formation but they will almost certainly not meet today's
grant deadline.
Within four years, therefore, Britain has gone from no machinery rings to
close to 30 and the majority of them have been set up during the last few
weeks. The ending of the grant had undoubtedly speeded their formation (it
has been available since 1986) but Pounds 3,333 per year for three years
split be-tween perhaps 200-300 farmers is insufficient motivation on its own
for what has happened.
The plain fact is that the machinery ring is an idea whose time has now come
in the UK. To some extent there is an element of following fashion because
the concept has received a great deal of publicity in recent months. The
main reason for the rush of activity, however, is declining farm profits and
the realisation by a growing number of farmers that they must cut their
costs to survive in business.
On average, the so-called 'variable costs' of running a farm - the money
spent on seeds, fertilisers, sprays and so on - amount to between 35 per
cent and 40 per cent of total costs. Fixed costs account for the remaining
60 per cent to 65 per cent and cover such things as labour, interest
charges, power and machinery.
In recent years, as margins have declined, some of these 'fixed costs' have
had to become variable as numbers of farmworkers have diminished either
through natural wastage or redundancy and as assets have been sold to reduce
borrowings and, therefore, interest charges. Power costs are more difficult
to control in the face of fluctuating oil prices while real depreciation on
machinery values can be horrendous.
Indeed, the depreciation rates typically used in farm accounts may well be
insufficient to allow for the replacement of machines whose purchase prices
continue to rise with inflation.
Add to that the fact that many farms are over-mechanised for the
understandable reason that farmers like to feel on top of any job, whatever
the weather, and it is clear that economies in machinery costs are overdue
in the current financial climate.
The machinery ring has obviously been recognised as a possible solution. For
Pounds 50 per year membership charge and a modest purchase of share capital,
a farmer can plug into a source of extra income or extra help, whichever he
prefers. Commission charges of 2 per cent are levied on both the demander
and the provider of the work to cover the costs of the co-ordinator and his
computer. Otherwise, the charges for work are set at similar rates to the
most competitive contractors.
Experience shows, apparently, that most rings lose money in their first year
or two but that as the organisation develops and as members begin to review
their machinery replacement policies, the flow of work offered and done
builds up dramatically. Indeed, it is possible to foresee situations where
some farmers decide to buy bigger machines than they can justify in order to
earn extra cash working on other members' farms. At the same time, other
farmers may see opportunities to earn more money off the farm and be pleased
to pay a ring member to do most of his farm work.
The pattern is already established in Germany, albeit on smaller farms than
are typical in the UK. It is yet another step towards the establishment of
significant numbers of part-time farmers in this country. In any event,
those groups of farmers who have their machinery rings up and running are
convinced that there is a potential for many more.
A couple of weeks ago, there was a meeting of machinery ring leaders at the
National Agricultural Centre at Stoneleigh, in Warwickshire. They decided to
set up an Association of Machinery Rings to guide those who come after and
to lobby on behalf of members on such things as the presently-restricted use
of red, tax-free diesel fuel in tractors travelling more than 15 miles from
their home base. They see this as a possible inhibition to the efficient
working of rings which may cover an area 30 to 40 miles wide.
The success of the concept relies on the willing co-operation of farmers. In
this country, agricultural co-operation, with a few notable exceptions, has
seldom succeeded beyond the first flush of enthusiasm. I believe this
machinery ring version of co-operation will work. In any case, the other day
I signed up to join one.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 30 Illustration (Omitted).
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>17</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAGBFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / Commodities and Agriculture: LME monitors copper market as
squeeze tightens
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By KENNETH GOODING, Mining Correspondent
</BYLINE>
<TEXT>
THE LONDON Metal Exchange executive yesterday said it was carefully
monitoring events in the copper market where a technical squeeze has been
causing severe volatility.
As the squeeze reached its climax yesterday the price of borrowing (buying
cash and selling forward) for one day reached Pounds 40 a tonne.
During recent upheavals in the zinc market, the LME executive persuaded
those with metal to lend to restrict the cost of borrowing for a day to
Dollars 20 a tonne and some dealers asked last night why the cost of
borrowing copper had been allowed to rise much more substantially.
Mr Martin Abbott, the LME's director of marketing, said: 'Our duty is to run
an orderly market - not to limit the cost of borrowing or the back-wardation
(the premium for metal for immediate delivery compared with the three-month
price).'
Copper's backwardation widened to Pounds 100 a tonne at one stage yesterday
and traders said this would continue to stimulate a flood of the metal into
LME warehouse stocks. Copper stocks already stood at 261,775 tonnes at the
weekend, the highest total for seven years, and traders estimated that
today's stock report would show a further increase of about 10,000 tonnes.
Mr Abbott said however, that, although the LME's copper stocks were
relatively high, it would be wrong to assume that all the metal was
available to be sold on the market. The owners might well be 'parking' the
copper briefly in LME warehouses.
The copper market was going through a 'choppy period' of volatility because
there was still a split of opinion about whether there would be a surplus
this year, Mr Abbott suggested. This choppiness could go on for some time
before there was a clear consensus of opinion about the fundamental
direction of the market.
However, many analysts now insist that the recession which is begining to
make its mark on even the strongest economies will far outweigh any
interruptions to copper supplies this year.
In the latest Metals and Mining Monthly Update from Carr Kitcat &amp; Aitken,
part of the Banque Indosuez Group, analyst Mr Robin Bhar says key copper
consuming sectors in the US (construction, autos and capital goods) will
remain depressed and consumption in Germany is likely to be restrained by
slowing economic growth caused by the mounting costs of reunification.
Consequently, says Mr Bhar, copper stocks will keep rising during 1991 and
the price is likely to fall decisively below Dollars 1 a lb, perhaps to
between 70 cents and 80 cents a lb. The dollar price ended at Dollars 1.04 a
lb last night.
In sterling terms, cash copper ended at Pounds 1,443 a tonne, down Pounds
6.50 from Friday's close, while three-month metal was Pounds 1,346, down
Pounds 11.50.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 30
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>18</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAGAFT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / Commodities and Agriculture: Total in Algerian gas field
deal
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By GEORGE GRAHAM
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   PARIS
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
TOTAL, THE French state-controlled oil group, has signed a FFr3bn (Dollars
512m) agreement with Sonatrach, Algeria's state oil company, for the
development of the Hamra gas field, writes George Graham in Paris.
The French group will provide financing and technological assistance for the
development of the field, expected to start production in 1994.
In return, Total will have access to Hamra's entire output of condensates
and liquefied petroleum gas - an estimated 150m to 200m barrels petroleum
equivalent - for a period of 14 to 17 years.
The deal shows the continued willingness of big Western companies to invest
in Algeria, despite the political uncertainty that has been hanging over the
country's future since the rise of the fundamentalist Islamic Salvation
Front.
Total also agreed yesterday to renew for a further five years its joint
venture with Sonatrach for the operation of the Mereksen oil field, which
currently produces around 600,000 tonnes of oil a year. It also signed two
exploration contracts covering 6,458 square kilometres at Djebel Bottena and
Hamra Southeast.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 30
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>19</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF9FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / Commodities and Agriculture: Fuel cell use is predicted for
platinum
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By KENNETH GOODING, Mining Correspondent
</BYLINE>
<TEXT>
FUEL CELLS, environmentally friendly units which produce electricity and
heat from a controlled chemical reaction be-tween hydrogen and oxygen, are
likely to provide the next substantial industrial application for platinum,
according to Johnson Matthey, the world's biggest platinum marketing group.
By the end of this century about 200,000 troy ounces of platinum a year
could be ab-sorbed by this new market - about the same as the chemical and
electrical industries each use today, JM suggests in its annual review of
the market.
However, this could be a conservative estimate. If fuel cells incorporating
platinum catalysts are used and if the market develops as projected by the
Japanese Ministry of International Trade and Industry, annual demand for
platinum in that country alone by the year 2010 would be more than 400,000
ounces.
'Beyond the turn of the century platinum consumption could soar, should the
market for fuel cells in vehicles materialise and dreams of a hydrogen
economy become a reality,' says Mr Jeremy Coombes, author of the JM review.
The fuel cell is a prime contender to meet demand for electricity without
increasing pollution, he points out. It is versatile and efficient, produces
hardly any noxious emissions and so could help to re-solve the apparent
conflict between continued economic growth and the preservation of a healthy
environment.
Fuel cells went into commercial production for the first time last year.
Japan is showing the most commitment to their development. The Japanese
government is spending about Dollars 27m a year on research, and Fuji
Electric, Toshiba and Sanyo have developed marketable products and
established production lines to build them.
The US Department of Energy is currently spending Dollars 44m a year on fuel
cell research while spending in Europe is about Dollars 60m. By 1995 more
than 100 fuel cells will be installed and producing power in Europe, Japan,
the US and the Far East.
Mr Coombes says commercial units should be available in 1993 at a cost of
Dollars 1,500 per kilowat of generating capacity, not much more than the
cost from conventional generating plant, and the cost is likely to fall as
more fuel cells are built.
On the main features of the platinum market last year, the JM review
reports:
Demand for platinum in-creased by 5.5 per cent to a record 3.66m ounces.
Supplies rose by 9 per cent to 3.73m ounces.
The market moved into marginal oversupply of 70,000 ounces from a marginal
undersupply of 45,000 ounces in 1989. The slight oversupply might continue
for some years.
Supplies from South Africa, the world's biggest producer, were constrained
by production difficulties but grew modestly. Shipments to the west from the
Soviet Union, at 700,000 ounces, were the highest for 15 years.
This year JM expects platinum to trade at about Dollars 400 an ounce before
rising as the year progresses towards Dollars 450.
'Platinum 1991', free from Johnson Matthey, 78 Hatton Garden House, London
EC1N 8JP, England.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 30 Chart (Omitted). Graph (Omitted). Photograph Humbug Machine,
a Rowland Emett model powered by a fuel cell containing platinum catalysts
(Omitted).
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>20</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF8FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / International Capital Markets: Citicorp in asset-backed
launch worth Dollars 1.4bn
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By SIMON LONDON
</BYLINE>
<TEXT>
CITICORP yesterday launched its first global asset-backed bond issue since
August last year, a Dollars 1.4bn deal backed by a portfolio of credit card
receivables.
The progress of the deal confirmed that investors are once again willing to
buy asset-backed securities. This will encourage other financial
institutions looking to remove consumer finance assets from their balance
sheets through securitised bond offerings.
The five-year deal, lead-managed by Salomon Brothers, is backed by credit
card receivables in Citicorp's 'master trust' of credit card accounts.
The main portion of the deal, at Dollars 1.25bn, carries a triple-A credit
rating by virtue of an additional Dollars 155m subordinated tranche which
will absorb any initial losses of the master trust.
The deal will be priced today, with the senior notes at an indicated yield
spread of between 95 and 99 basis points over five-year US Treasury paper.
The subordinated bonds, which carry an A-2/A credit rating from US credit
rating agencies Moody's and Standard &amp; Poor's, will be priced at around 145
basis points over US Treasuries.
The lead manager said most of the international market tranche of the deal
was placed with institutional investors based in London. However, US
investors remain dominant buyers of mortgage-backed bonds, and most of the
subordinated paper was placed in the US.
Citicorp's last asset-backed deal in the international bond market was
launched in November. The deal was then priced to yield 90 basis points over
US Treasury securities, but the bonds traded out to well over 100 basis
points after launch.
Market sentiment, however, has been firmer over the past two months, and the
deal's pricing was considered attractive. In addition, the deal had been
widely anticipated in the market, and many investors had set aside funds to
buy the bonds. Demand was dominated by institutional investors.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 29
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>21</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF7FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / Government Bonds: Gilts follow Treasuries' fall in auction
aftermath
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By SARA WEBB, PATRICK HARVERSON and DAVID LASCELLES, Banking Editor
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   LONDON, NEW YORK
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
UK GOVERNMENT bonds plummeted yesterday morning, responding to the sharp
fall in the US Treasury bond market on Friday afternoon.
The benchmark 11 3/4 per cent Treasury stock due 2003/07 opened at 110 9/32
and fell to a low of 109 1/2 before recovering in the afternoon.
Traders said the disappointing UK credit business figures released
yesterday, which were slightly higher than market expectations, may have
helped to depress prices.
The gilts market is this week waiting for the release of several important
economic indicators which could determine whether the Bank of England
decides to cut the base rate. These include the producer prices index for
April today, the unemployment figures on Thursday, and the retail prices
index on Friday.
THE US government bond market remained unsettled yesterday in the wake of
Friday's frenzied sell-off, but prices at the long end did gain ground on
the back of some sporadic buying.
In late trading, the benchmark 30-year Treasury issue was up 1 7/32 at 98
13/32 , to yield 8.264 per cent. The two-year note was up  1/16 at 100 5/16
, yielding 6.808 per cent. Trading activity was exceptionally light.
Dealers and investors continued to digest the implications of the dramatic
fall in prices which followed last week's difficult auction of Dollars 37bn
in government securities. With a large chunk of that paper still to be
distributed, analysts were not expecting any significant recovery in bond
values in the near term.
The day's only economic news had little impact on sentiment. The Federal
Reserve reported that industrial production rose 0.1 per cent in April,
after falling a revised 0.6 per cent in March.
THE Italian government bond market jumped yesterday following the
one-percentage point cut in the discount rate at the weekend.
The cut, from 12.5 to 11.5 per cent, followed the cabinet's approval of
L14,000bn in spending cuts and revenue increases to curb the public deficit.
Yields fell across the range of maturities as retail buyers scrambled to buy
bonds. The yield on the 12.5 per cent bond due 2001 fell from 13.35 per cent
to 13.07 per cent.
The Bank of Italy's decision to cut the reserve requirement on the net
increase in banks' and credit institutions' foreign currency deposits, with
effect from the June reserve month, was seen as a bullish factor by the
market. The move should free around L5,000bn of funds for use by the credit
system.
The cut in the Italian discount rate buoyed hopes of interest rate cuts in
the Spanish and French government bond markets
The Spanish bond market saw strong buying interest among the shorter-dated
maturities. The yield on Spain's 13.45 per cent government bond due April
1996 fell from 11.91 to 11.82 per cent as foreign buyers moved in, hoping to
benefit from an expected cut in the intervention rate.
The Bank of Spain left its key money market rate unchanged at 13.5 per cent
at its repurchase tender for central bank certificates. Traders said that
this was disappointing, but did not rule out the possibility of an interest
rate cut soon.
Other European government bond markets opened weak in the wake of the US
Treasury bond market's fall on Friday.
The German market was haunted yet again by the rumour that Bundesbank
president, Mr Karl Otto Pohl, may step down. Bund prices fell after the US
decline, with the longer maturities taking the brunt of the fall. Despite
some buying interest in short and medium-dated bunds, they ended almost
unchanged on the day.
JAPANESE government bonds rallied as a fall in short-term interest rates
rekindled hopes of a cut in the official discount rate.
The overnight unsecured call rate was cut from 8 3/16 to 8 1/16 per cent,
while the rate on three-month certificates of deposit fell from 7.9 to 7.83
per cent. The fall was interpreted by some traders as a possible sign of the
Bank of Japan easing monetary policy. The yen weakened against the dollar
due to the lower interest rates, and traders said the Bank of Japan
intervened to buy yen and sell dollars yesterday.
The bond rally was short-lived, and JGB prices closed almost unchanged as
attention later in the day focused on a number of Euroyen issues, including
one of Y50bn by the World Bank. The benchmark No 129 JGB opened with a yield
of 6.635 per cent, moving to 6.605 per cent before closing in Tokyo at 6.63.
Barclays de Zoete Wedd, the investment banking arm of the Barclays group,
has obtained a seat on the Frankfurt Stock Exchange through its
newly-acquired German investment bank, Merck, Finck, writes David Lascelles,
Banking Editor.
Skandinaviska Enskilda Banken (S-E-Banken) will use the trading name
Scandinvanian Bank for its branch in London. S-E-Banken bought Scandinavian
Banking Group, the London consortium bank, last year and its licence is
being surrendered.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 28 Table (Omitted).
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>22</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF6FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / International Company News: USF&amp;G to bolster capital by
Dollars 300m stock issues
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By NIKKI TAIT
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   NEW YORK
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
USF&amp;G, the large but troubled US insurance group, yesterday revealed plans
to bolster its capital base by raising up to Dollars 300m through issues of
convertible preferred stock.
Last month, the Baltimore-based multiline insurer said that it would cut its
workforce by around a quarter in a major 'downsizing' of its business.
It is also in the midst of reorganising its operational structure so that
its commercial and personal lines become two separate businesses with
independent profit centres.
The company announced a Dollars 569m loss last year, and has already cut its
quarterly dividend from 73 cents a share to 5 cents a share.
A new chairman, Mr Norman Blake, was brought into the company in November,
and other management changes have followed.
USF&amp;G said yesterday that the majority of the proceeds of the new issues
would be used 'to strengthen the surplus of the primary unit, United States
Fidelity and Guaranty Company'.
It anticipated that the funds would be raised via the issue of two series of
convertible prefered stock. These would be sold to investors both through a
public offering and through a separate private placement.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 27
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>23</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF5FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / International Company News: Toyoda machinery sales surge
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By ROBERT THOMSON
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   TOKYO
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
TOYODA Automatic Loom Works, a leading member of the Toyota Motor group,
reported an 11.1 per cent increase in pre-tax profit to Y30.2bn (Dollars
218.84m) for the year to end-March, as sales of automobile assembly
equipment rose with the expansion of vehicle production at Toyota.
The company, the first founded of the Toyota group, reported an 18.8 per
cent increase in sales to Y583.69bn, with a 33.5 per cent surge in textile
machinery sales, a 28.2 per cent rise in automobile assembly equipment, and
an 8.8 per cent improvement in industrial vehicles.
Company officials said personnel expenses rose during the year because of
Japan's labour shortage, and earnings were affected by the increase in the
country's interest rates, but they added that the advance in sales more than
compensated for those costs.
However, Japan's vehicle market has softened and export markets are also
troubled, so sales for this year are expected to rise only 4.5 per cent to
Y610bn, while pre-tax profit is predicted to fall 2.3 per cent to Y29.5bn,
the first fall in five years.
Toyota Tsusho, a trading arm of the Toyota group, reported a 10.8 per cent
lift in sales to Y2,163bn, while pre-tax profit increased 4.5 per cent to
Y16.16bn.
Domestic sales advanced 10.4 per cent, while foreign trade increased 11.6
per cent, with exports up 19 per cent, imports down 0.5 per cent, and trade
between third world countries up 16.4 per cent.
The company expects a 6.2 per cent increase in sales to Y2,300bn this year
and an 11.4 per cent rise in pre-tax profit to Y18bn, despite higher labour
costs and a heavier interest payment burden.
Another Toyota affiliate, Aisin Seiki, is expecting a decline in recurring
profit from the Y20.2bn in the year to end-March, up 1.1 per cent on 1989,
to around Y17bn for the present year.
The company announced yesterday that sales for the year to end-March rose
14.5 per cent to Y525bn, with those of automobile parts up 14.8 per cent to
Y495.7bn and household machinery rising 10.1 per cent to Y29.2bn.
Sales for the current year are expected to increase 4.7 per cent to Y550bn,
but the expected downturn in profits is attributed to the sluggish car
market, and increased depreciation and personnel expenses.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 27
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>24</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF4FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / International Company News: Nordstrom boosts earnings
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By KAREN ZAGOR
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   NEW YORK
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
NORDSTROM, the Seattle-based retailer managed by the founding Nordstrom
family, yesterday turned in sharply higher first-quarter earnings and said
it had settled federal and state securities class action lawsuits for
Dollars 7.5m.
Mr John Goesling, Nordstrom's senior vice-president, said the results
'compare favourably with what we regarded as a disappointing performance
during the previous year's first quarter.'
Net income leapt 95 per cent to Dollars 25.7m, or 31 cents a share, from
Dollars 13.2m, or 16 cents, a year earlier. Net sales grew 10 per cent in
the three months to Dollars 610.6m from Dollars 555m.
Shares in Nordstrom jumped Dollars 2 3/4 to Dollars 44 yesterday in active
over-the-counter trading. The company attributed its improved performance to
improving sales trends, better management of inventories and steps taken in
the previous year to reduce operating expenses.
During the quarter, Nordstrom reduced its selling, general and
administrative expenses to 27.65 per cent of sales from 29.4 per cent a year
earlier.
Pre-tax earnings jumped 101 per cent to Dollars 41.4m, or 6.77 per cent of
sales, from Dollars 20.6m, or 3.71 per cent of sales, a year earlier.
Nordstrom also said yesterday that it had settled a number of lawsuits
alleging that the company and six of its officers failed to disclose that
Nordstrom might be liable for additional employee compensation arising from
Nordstrom's past employee practices.
In the last year, Nordstrom's reputation has been clouded by a union dispute
and by revelations that the company's commission sales force is not properly
compensated.
Mr Goesling said: 'While we have not yet resolved with our insurance company
their share of this settlement, we are confident that any payment made by
the company will not have a material effect on the results of operations for
the year.'
The settlement, which is subject to court approval, provides for payment of
Dollars 7.5m to shareholders who bought Nordstrom stock between February 1
1988 and March 8 1990.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 27
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>25</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF3FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / International Company News: Two Venezuelan airlines register
losses
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By JOE MANN
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   CARACAS
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
THE TWO state-owned Venezuelan airlines due to be privatised this year
suffered financial losses in 1990, according to figures published by the
Ministry of Transportation and Communications.
Viasa, the government's international flag-carrier, lost USDollars 34m in
1990 on overall revenues of Dollars 268m, compared with Dollars 4.6m profit
in 1989 on revenues of Dollars 266.7m.
Another state-owned airline, Aeropostal, which flies domestic and
international routes, suffered a 1990 loss of Dollars 7.3m on revenues of
Dollars 82.1m.
In 1989, Aeropostal reported net earnings of Dollars 2.8m on revenues which
totalled Dollars 68.8m. (Dollar figures were calculated using free-market
exchange rates for the Venezuelan bolivar at the end of each year.)
The government of President Carlos Andres Perez is keen to privatise Viasa
and Aeropostal this year to demonstrate that its slow-moving privatisation
programme is finally getting off the ground.
Since the government took office over two years ago, it has privatised only
two commercial banks from a long list of companies it plans to sell off.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 27
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>26</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF2FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / International Company News: SA Brewing expands in US water
heating
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By KEVIN BROWN
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   SYDNEY
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
SA BREWING Holdings, the diversified Adelaide-based brewing and
manufacturing group, yesterday said it had more than doubled its share of
the US water heater market through the USDollars 31.65m acquisition of
Mor-Flo Industries.
SA Brewing said the acquisition would give it 30 per cent of the US market
for mains pressure water heaters, which accounts for around 7.6m units a
year.
The group entered the US water heaters market in 1989 thorough the purchase
of Bradford-White Corporation of Michigan, which claimed around 12 per cent
of the market.
The deal, which is subject to US regulatory approval, is expected to be
concluded in August.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 27
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>27</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF1FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / International Company News: Fletcher Challenge shares placed
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By TERRY HALL
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   WELLINGTON
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
FLETCHER Challenge (FCL) yesterday announced it had successfully placed
NZDollars 195m (USDollars 115m) worth of shares with international
institutional investors in a move designed to ease its debt burden.
However, the company did not announce the fate of a further 25m shares which
were being offered as oversubscriptions and were not underwritten. It is
hoped these shares would raise the total to NZDollars 292.5m.
News of the unexpected placement forced the share prices sharply lower
yesterday, ending a month-long rally. FCL dropped 22 cents to NZDollars
3.92, which was 2 cents above the placement price for the 50m shares. The
placement was underwritten by brokers CS First Boston NZ and Potter Warburg
Markets.
Mr Hugh Fletcher, FCL chief executive officer, said the placement showed
international investors strongly supported the New Zealand company which has
diverse holdings in the forestry products and building materials industries.
An FCL spokesman said the additional funds would represent a reduction in
group debt levels of about 1.4 per cent.
The company last month revised its forecasts, warning that full-year profits
might be about 10 per cent below the NZDollars 662.4m for the year to June
30 1990.
FCL, the second largest newsprint producer in the world, has suffered from
declining demand for its paper and a drop in prices for pulp and timber.
The spokesman said capital spending peaked last year at NZDollars 1.3bn and
was expected to fall to about NZDollars 800m. He said the group had to sell
all its property interests, valued at about NZDollars 500m held through
Fletcher Construction and Challenge Properties.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 27
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<DOC>
<DOCNO>28</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>_AN-BENBQAF0FT</PROFILE>
<DATE>910514
</DATE>
<HEADLINE>
FT  14 MAY 91 / International Company News: Aerolneas Argentinas sale enters
final phase
</HEADLINE>
<BYLINE>
   By JOHN BARHAM
</BYLINE>
<DATELINE>
   BUENOS AIRES
</DATELINE>
<TEXT>
THE privatisation of Aerolneas Argentinas, the Argentine national airline,
entered its final phase yesterday, six months after the government and an
international consortium exchanged contracts.
The consortium, led by Spain's Iberia, delivered Dollars 810m-worth of
foreign debt certificates to the government as part of an agreement reached
between the two sides in April.
The privatisation stalled earlier this year after the government and
consortium members squabbled over the terms of the contract. The buyers
refused to pay, while the government refused to deliver the 85 per cent of
Aerolineas shares on sale.
Under the new agreement, the consortium agreed to deliver Dollars 1.61bn in
foreign debt paper in two tranches. It has also provided satisfactory
guarantees from international banks underpinning its Dollars 540m investment
plan in Aerolneas, as required by the original contract.
Earlier, the buyers paid Dollars 142m in government dollar-denominated bonds
worth 68 per cent of face value on the local market, replacing Dollars 130m
in deferred payments due under the original contract.
</TEXT>
<PUB>The Financial Times
</PUB>
<PAGE>
London Page 26
</PAGE>
</DOC>
<!-- tambahan -->

<DOC>
<DOCNO>251</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>D.H.E 45-FDA (Dihydroergotamine)
</PROFILE>

<HEADLINE>dihydroergotamine mesylate, USP 1 mg, methanesulfonic acid/sodium hydroxide, qs to pH 3.6  0. 4 6.1 % by vol. glycerin, UP 15% by wt. water for injection, USP , qs to 1 ml.</HEADLINE>

<TEXT>
D.H.E. 45  (dihydroergotamine mesylate) Injection, USP is indicated for the acute treatment of migraine headaches with or without aura and the acute treatment of cluster headache episodes.</TEXT>

</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>252</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Dacarbazine(Dtic - FDA Dome)
</PROFILE>

<HEADLINE>
100 mg of dacarbazine, or 200 mg of dacarbazine (the active ingredient), anhydrous citric acid and mannitol</HEADLINE>

<TEXT>
DTlC-Dome is indicated in the treatment of metastatic malignant melanoma. In addition, DTlC-Dome is also indicated for Hodgkin's disease as a second-line therapy when used in combination with other effective agents.ns.</TEXT>

</DOC>


<DOC>
<DOCNO>252</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Dacarbazine(Dtic - FDA Dome)
</PROFILE>

<HEADLINE>
100 mg of dacarbazine, or 200 mg of dacarbazine (the active ingredient), anhydrous citric acid and mannitol</HEADLINE>

<TEXT>
DTlC-Dome is indicated in the treatment of metastatic malignant melanoma. In addition, DTlC-Dome is also indicated for Hodgkin's disease as a second-line therapy when used in combination with other effective agents.ns.</TEXT>

</DOC>



<DOC>
<DOCNO>252</DOCNO>
<PROFILE>Dacarbazine(Dtic - FDA Dome)
</PROFILE>

<HEADLINE>
100 mg of dacarbazine, or 200 mg of dacarbazine (the active ingredient), anhydrous citric acid and mannitol</HEADLINE>

<TEXT>
DTlC-Dome is indicated in the treatment of metastatic malignant melanoma. In addition, DTlC-Dome is also indicated for Hodgkin's disease as a second-line therapy when used in combination with other effective agents.ns.</TEXT>

</DOC>



<!-- akhir tambahan -->
</NEWS>